https://www.stlcosmeticsurgery.com/privacy-statement/

HomePrivacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Overview of Information Collection and Use
St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery, a private practice operating in the state of Missouri, uses the following set of privacy principles:
1. The only information St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery obtains about individual visitors to its Web site is that which is supplied voluntarily by visitors.
2. Personally identifiable information (name, e-mail or home address, etc.) will not be disclosed to anyone other than the physicians and staff of St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery, unless visitors indicate that they may do so.
Log Files and IP Addresses
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. stlcosmeticsurgery.com collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, evaluate aggregate such as total traffic to the site, and conduct site analysis.
If a visitor requests (clicks on links to) pages within St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery, the stlcosmeticsurgery.com servers enter the visitor’s IP address into a log. To maintain visitor anonymity, St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery does not associate IP addresses with records containing personal information. However, we do use IP addresses to identify any visitors who refuse to comply with our in-house rules or terms of service, and to identify visitors who threaten our service, site, customers or others.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery does not use cookies.
External (Destination) Links
In order to provide visitors with greater value, the physicians at St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery may provide links to various third party Web sites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between this site and that destination site, St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery exercises no authority over linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures.
St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery assumes no responsibility or liability for these sites’ independent methods or actions and is not responsible for the independent policies or procedures of destination sites. Similarly, we cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such Web sites. These destination links are provided only for your convenience; access them at your own risk.
Opt-In E-Newsletters
St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery may provide visitors the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications, mostly in the form of an e-newsletter. All recipients of such a communication provide their contact information at will; in other words, these communications are sent to those who have given permission to receive them.
Further, visitors have the freedom to opt-out from these communications at any time, by following the instructions at the end of each communication. If you have any difficulty dis-engaging from these communiqués, you have the following options:
1. You can send an email here.
2. You can send mail to the following postal address: 17300 N Outer 40 Road, Suite 300, Chesterfield, MO 63005.
3. You can call the following telephone number:
(636) 530-6161
Security Measures
St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery does not use encrypted messaging. Any message sent over email has the possibility, albeit small, to be intercepted by a third party.
St. Louis Cosmetic Surgery maintains strict policies about which staff and other parties may view patient identifiable information. If you wish to request a copy of our internal policy, please contact us.
Contacting Us About Privacy Issues
If you have any questions about the our privacy statement, the practices of this Web site, or your interaction with this Web site, contact us.
COVID-19 UPDATE:
We have reopened! Please review our safety protocols before coming to the practice.
We are offering virtual consultations. Please contact the office to schedule your consultation today.
Learn More
Virtual Consultations
